what is good guys welcome back to the
channel we got another video where you
guys already know dropping a video every
tuesday every friday i usually drop
educational videos kind of like chart
breakdowns uh trades that i'm looking
for the future um if it's not something
educational you know little sneak peeks
in my strategy um it's a fire setup
forget podcast stay tuned to this
friday's podcast it's gonna be my first
episode of
uh psychology every other episode has
been straight entrepreneurs just
interviews now this is gonna be very
much different it's just gonna be
strictly psychology if you guys wanna
see part one make sure to go check out
the channel like comment and subscribe
so this video is gonna be very simple
what is better mt4 or nt5 so i got this
question asked a lot when i recently
switched over to a new broker um at the
time the broker was only offering mt5
right and i originally traded mt4 i
personally actually never traded on mt5
um but the broker they it was just they
were giving me you know zero commission
raw spreads and you know the because i
have an affiliation link in the link
description below you guys want to know
more about the broker the link is in the
description the like what they were
offering me and my community i was like
bro i gotta take the deal you know if i
have to switch over to mt5 that's fine
you know what's the big deal it can't
really make them that much of a
difference and it's actually not that
much of a difference in this video i'm
going to actually be showing you guys
the only differences that mt4 and mt5
have which in my opinion are basically
nothing to kind of round it up very
simple
mt4 is let's just say a 2017
car the nt5 is a 2022 it's just the
newer version of the previous car it's
the same exact model just looks a little
bit cooler so now i'm going to pop up on
the screen mt4 right so we all know mt4
for the videos that didn't know there
was an mt3 metatrader metatrader3 i bet
a lot of you guys didn't know i didn't
know that until i started digging and
doing my own research on this so what
happened is when nt4 came out and the
mt3 went bust so now supposedly mt4 is
going to go bust and then mt5 is going
to be the new one whatever the case is
it doesn't really matter because the
broker that i use offers both as the
majority of the brokers should so as you
can tell here uh this is metatrader4 um
this is just kind of like a little you
know basic uh quote section then we
obviously have the charts this is a
trade this is not my account size i will
not show my account size this is just a
leveled up account you guys know raul
and i we came up uh we have founded and
created level of society where we're
literally funding traders building
literally a society of traders so yes i
trade on my own funding company um so as
you can tell this is like just the basic
uh metatrader4 as you can tell this is
what everybody knows so if we were to go
to mt5 now
you guys can tell that it's a little bit
different so um it looks a lot more
modern it looks a lot more you know
defined cooler if you guys you know want
to get all technical but it has the same
concept as you can tell to the bottom
left is still quotes this one is still
charts this one is still trade it's
still history this is just still all the
same all around so this is honestly to
me just a much more modern version as
you can tell the letters here are a lot
cleaner um than versus mt4 i think i
believe
that when it comes to mt5 i know you can
adjust your stop loss and your take
profit on your chart that is not
something that i have actually tried
i've had my students in the community i
think tell me that they've done it or i
think that's ctrader i'm not entirely
sure don't uh don't quote me on that
i've personally never done it just you
know to keep an eye actually probably
test it out later on tonight if i end up
trading with this thing with the signal
group but yeah basically it's just a lot
more cooler version i personally don't
see anything other different than that
if you were to choose versus mt4 or mt5
i would probably pick mt5 just because
if the same concept happens that now mt4
kind of goes away and then it's only mt5
uh versus how it was mt3 and now it's
only mt4 i would start getting used to
uncomfortable with mt5 but it's really
not a big difference um but yeah that's
pretty very simple video i feel like i
want to make a video of it maybe i come
across any beginners that are kind of
like still confused on their journey on
exactly what to do so i feel this video
was helpful for you guys so if there's
any other things kind of in the forex
world that you guys are unsure of
whether it's like any any other tools
that you need in our essentials to trade
just drop a comment you know this is
what i do like i trade forex this is
like my life like everything that i do
revolves around forks so i'm pretty sure
i know the ins and outs to everything um
with that being said make sure to watch
the podcast this friday where i'm going
to be hosting my first psychology uh
webinar which i think is going to be
fire like nobody ever before so with
that being said make sure to like
comment and subscribe and i'll see you
guys in the next video